Visit our website for more: turkision.com
No living being was harmed during
the filming of this series.
Episode 118
It's good that we took...
Nayman's courage from him.
And the people saw the defeat of those
who are said to be invincible.
They are the ones
who will move now.
What will their next campaign be?
Soldiers are spread around the
districts of Candar and Karesi.
It is clear that they are after revenge.
They will want to strike back
with a bloody attack, Osman Bey.
If that was his goal...
he'd have wanted then to destroy everyone
with the armies of the Beys here.
He wants us...
who don't obey...
and who rebel.
We have basically
destroyed the Nayman's army.
His strength was no longer
what it was before on this earth.
He'll want his strength back.
He'll want to attack us with Olof.
But he will not move until
he is sure that he will win.
He attacked Olof several times.
He has become weak militarily.
With what force will they
unite and move against us?
Olof is the successor of Kantakuzenos.
The emperor believed that he would
protect the inheritance of Aya Nikola.
The emperor must
have sent an army to him.
So getting İnegöl back just got harder.
It's just the right time
to take inegöl back.
We'll take it one way or another.
There is no other solution.
Otherwise, Nayman will unite
with Olof's army.
Okay, but how will that be done, my Bey?
İnegöl Castle
Osman took you from me.
My younger brother.
Don't worry, Dan.
I will capture
all his children.
And I will fill my mug with their blood.
I will make them live in hell.
We will organize a funeral
worthy of knights.
Tell those in the church...
for them to prepare.
Olof.
Dan never believed in your religion.
He pretended this just for you.
Let him go to Valhalla.
How did you know?
Jesus will embrace Dan.
We will avenge him.
Neither Odin nor Jesus.
I believe in revenge now.
We will be together so that we can take revenge.
What shall we do? Say it.
Osman did not burn
our souls only.
We will take our revenge with those
who are angry with him.
Who are they?
Commander Nayman is coming.
Olof.
Nayman must have reached İnegöl by now.
But he isn't the only one who
gets inside.
Cerkutay and Ülgen have
been in it for a while now.
That is why we pounce on Olof
on all his campaigns, Öktem Bey.
Thanks to them both.
Turgut knows the castle best.
Turgut, take some warriors with you.
Don't worry.
Cerkutay will help you get inside.
I will do as you said.
It's time, Ülgen.
We will make İnegöl our home again.
We will return to Yenişehir.
Truly? Is this correct?
Will our job end?
It will be over, Ülgen, it
will be over.
Osman Bey lit the fire of conquest.
And he informed us of our mission.
We will open the gates of İnegöl.
Thank Allah, the longing will end.
Thank Allah.
Listen to me carefully now.
We'll get Turgut Bey and
his warriors inside first...
secretly.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
But taking İnegöl will only stop Nayman.
What are we going to do to eliminate
Nayman? Tell us about this.
Everyone will work.
The campaign (move)
that will stop Nayman...
I will keep it a secret.
What is our campaign now?
We will unite with Mother Sultan.
How will we convince
Mother Sultan, Osman Bey?
While Beys want to solve their
affairs with gold coins...
Sultan Mother wanted to gather armies.
When I cut off Samagar's head...
It was Mother Sultan who stood behind me.
Even if what you say is a
reason to convince her...
İsmihan can never be trusted.
We don't have to trust Mother Sultan.
But if she's on our side...
Then Nayman's job
will become harder.
Because
Mother Sultan is now on Nayman's side.
If we take her to our side...
Then we will be stronger.
If our matter remains for Mother Sultan,
then be careful not to lose our heads early.
We call this a prayer, Öktem Bey.
You are right, Turgut Bey,
you are right.
Osman Bey.
I will start preparations for the infiltration
to İnegöl with my warriors.
May our conquest be blessed.
- Boran.
- My Bey.
Send Alps to the sites
of Çamönü and Kızılağaç.
You will lead them.
Increase the measures.
They will attack us from all directions.
Your command, my Bey.
Let's go.
When will your army come?
My army will be here in a few days.
And when my army comes, I will
destroy Osman's tribe and his city.
Osman knows that we will attack him.
He posted guards around his tribe.
He set traps around it.
- He did the same in Yenişehir.
- We have a large number.
What trap can stop us?
Do you know the tale of the deer, Olof?
Five hungry wolves...
they smelled deer.
And they went after it.
Don't go, said the old wolf.
But the young wolves went.
When it was morning...
All the wolves were dead.
And the deer was looking at the old wolf.
How did this happen?
Let us know.
The mountain was not for wolves.
It was for deer.
It knows the abyss.
It knows the straits in it.
When the tribe that
Osman traps is destroyed...
You won't have anything left.
There is no need.
Commander Nayman.
What do you suggest?
Women speak little
when in captivity.
But she doesn't shut up when she's free,
does she, Olof?
I'm Frigg.
I know Yenişehir very well.
I took the goods
to deceive them.
You will tell me, woman.
You were with them for a long time.
What do we need for
the blockade of Yenişehir?
Show us the sites around Yenişehir.
How many people protect
its exits and entrances?
At Çamönü...
There are old warriors who
call themselves Ghazi.
They are skilled warriors,
attacking them is difficult.
But when we eliminate them,
we will have a great advantage.
Woman, if you are
going to say such things...
you can always speak.
You will destroy this village, Olof.
You will turn Ghazis into martyrs.
They won't live until tomorrow.
First, we will besiege Yenişehir.
Place your soldiers at
the exits of the tribe...
Olof.
Whoever exits, do not
allow him to enter again.
Whoever comes out of the tribe will
go under the dirt, Commander Nayman.
Destroy and destroy and erase!
Make the bravest fear, Olof.
What will you do in this
situation, Commander?
I'll take their most valuable possession.
I will strike Osman from a
place he never expects.
Come on, let's get started.
Yenişehir
Since you two summoned me in such a hurry,
you must have determined my punishment, right?
We thought a lot.
And we found a suitable punishment for you,
Bengi Hatun.
You are going to İnegöl.
Why?
You made Esma work as a spy for you.
Yes.
Now you're going to work as a spy for us,
Bengi Hatun.
You'll bring Frigg to us.
Do you hear what you're saying, Hatuns?
How will that happen?
Frigg won't trust me anymore.
You'll think about it
from now on, Bengi Hatun.
Osman Bey
will take İnegöl, Bengi Hatun.
Don't you want revenge on Olof?
We'll get Frigg and her soldiers out of
the palace first and reduce their number.
Now, say it, Bengi Hatun.
Are you with us?
Söğüt
What's the situation, Bayındır?
Not enough, Mother Sultan.
Our losses are many.
I don't want to say it...
but we had to listen to Osman.
Choosing war, not reconciliation.
Surrendering to someone like Nayman...
I find this very humiliating.
Anyway.
Put these with the rest.
Mother Sultan.
Osman Bey came and asked to see you.
Osman Bey is a good man.
We mentioned his name, and he came.
Let him in.
What's the point of coming to me
after you burned Nayman's headquarters?
Do you want to drag me
into the fire that will burn you?
You say exactly what is on my mind,
Mother Sultan.
Do you know what Nayman thinks?
He wants your head because of your
rebellion and because you killed Samagar.
and he wants to
take the gold coins, of course.
Why did Samagar die?
İnegöl Castle
Bengi.
So you came to your death with your feet,
right?
You pulled me into a trap.
Don't be stupid, Frigg.
Would you have made us bait for Nayman
in the caravansary?
I don't know about the caravansary.
I saved you.
If I'm going to drag you into a trap,
what am I doing here?
I brought you out
unharmed from that tribe.
If I wanted to, I would kill you there.
Why did you come?
You owe me your soul.
I want a price for that.
Look, look.
What do you want? Tell me.
Something that works for both of us.
I want to kill
Osman's sons.
Why?
Why do you want this?
Or are you going to trap me in a new trap?
Why do you think I let
my daughter marry Aktemur?
In order for Aktemur to become a Bey,
Orhan and Aladdin must die first.
But if I do this myself,
my plan will be exposed.
Now, you can do this
for revenge.
There is revenge I want
to take from Osman.
But you'll help me with this, Bengi.
Hear me well now.
It all started with the matter
of the throne.
Nayman wants your son Aladdin's throne.
Dazan Khan's conversion to Islam
will anger him.
If we don't unite...
Konya and these border areas
will be easy preys for him.
It was you who always spoiled the unit,
Osman Bey.
I established the unit and
established the army.
Well, what happened to the army?
You made a mistake, Mother Sultan.
You made us bow our
necks to the oppressor.
There will be no mistakes
anymore.
I will fight for the safety
of the border areas.
And you will fight for
Konya's freedom.
Are you offering to unite?
The time for the offer
has passed.
You will unite with me.
What if I don't?
I don't trust Bengi, my love.
I can't sacrifice you
for Dan's revenge.
That snake had its eye on the Beyhood.
She can't dare to deceive me.
But don't worry, my love.
I will get my soldiers
into the city already.
And I will take the sons
of Osman from him.
However, be careful, Frigg.
Odin will bring death to the Turks today.
We will burn them and destroy them.
We will kill them with pleasure.
If we don't unite...
Then they will burn us.
They will.
distract us.
Olof with whom you collaborated...
unites with Nayman.
The emperor will send an army for him.
They will unite and will want to burn
the border areas first.
And then, when they can't
get any support from Konya...
They will attack your son Aladdin.
How can you be so sure?
I haven't been wrong yet.
As for you, I never saw
you made the right choice.
Mother Sultan.
Well, what if I'm right
again?
What do you want from me?
We'll take İnegöl.
We will prevent the union of Nayman
with Olof's army.
But what I want from you is...
to look like you're loyal to Nayman now.
When we attack İnegöl,
I want you and your army to be with me.
You say Olof will be a trouble for us.
You say Konya is in danger...
and border areas as well.
Do you leave me
another choice, Osman Bey?
No.
No, Mother Sultan.
I will be waiting for you in Karayaz near
İnegöl at sunrise.
What if I come in there with the
Nayman army and destroy you?
How do you trust me, Osman Bey?
There is nothing you can not do
for your son, Mother Sultan.
You will stand behind
me for Sultan Aladdin.
You have no other solution.
I'm going to İnegöl tomorrow.
Olof still listens my words.
I'll try to take İnegöl with a game and
without bloodshed.
Mother Sultan.
Everything that has happened to us so far
has been due to games.
Let hit go.
Leave it, if blood will be spilled.
Let it shed.
When you come,
I'll be inside.
If blood will be spilled,
I will spill the first drop.
Take care.
Take care, Osman Bey..
Çamönü site (district)
Attack!
Leave no one alive!
Where are you coming from?
From Kargın tribe.
We brought Öktem Bey's goods.
Search them.
Bengi Hatun is waiting for us.
Go.
Open your eyes well.
Osman's sons may be anywhere.
Warriors!
We should know if a bird flies by.
Olof attacks Çamönü district.
Come on, my brothers, come on!
Come, my daughter, come!
Brothers, be alert!
Allah is the greatest!
My Bey, we have taken out the
women and children.
Ghazis!
Alps, step back, come on!
Let's go!
They think they have escaped from me.
I will burn their lands.
I will behead them all.
Get together, we'll go.
Alps.
Open your eyes well.
Take action, come on.
Let's go.
You two ugly little ones.
Trap!
Where are you going, Frigg?
Bengi, I'll make you pay for this.
Game over, Frigg.
You came for your death
with your own feet, Frigg.
It's over now.
You will die.
Do you think I don't know
you ambushed me?
Come here!
We'll send you and
your foxes to hell today.
Come on, Sisters.
Your end has come, Frigg.
You can't kill me.
I know everything about İsmihan.
You fools need me.
I will kill you all.
Shut up!
You shouldn't have touched my children.
Aktemur.
Are all the Alps and Sisters
in their places?
They're all alert, Malhun Hatun.
Good.
What happened, Malhun?
What happened?
Osman.
Olof destroyed Çamönü.
What are you saying?
He made a big raid.
Dog!
He would like to avenge
himself from the oppressed, then.
Fortunately, we had taken
measures.
Boran and Konur are also
at that site. (district.)
As he has done this to innocent people...
I will charge him double for that.
Everyone is on top of
their duties, My Bey.
The female warriors (Sisters) struck first.
The ladies had lured Frigg into an ambush.
They must've cut off her head by now.
Inshallah.
Alps!
Sisters!
You are fine, right?
Thank you, my Bey.
Oh, my baby, oh my baby.
Come on, come on.
Aktemur, come on, take
the wounded to the infirmary.
Your command, my Bey, come on.
Let's go.
Son.
Son, you are fine, right?
Thank you, my Bey.
Warriors!
Bandage your wounds and come to the court,
I am also going there.
Your command, my Bey.
Bala.
Here comes the Sisters who
cut the neck of the oppressor.
We crushed the head of the snake
with our Sisters, my Bey.
Mashallah.
Thank Allah.
Come on, my lion, come on.
- Come on.
Thank you.
İnegöl Castle
Nun Irene.
Where are you?
I am here!
Stop!
Where are you?
I looked for you everywhere!
I am on top of my mission.
I've been checking
the corridors.
There are a lot of soldiers in the lower
corridor while the upper one is empty.
Mashallah.
You did this spy business well!
You're my student.
Yes, I am the daughter
of a black maid.
Come on, we still
have a lot of work to do.
Let's get to the corridor first.
We'll still get Turgut Bey inside.
Let's go.
I got those.
You guard me from behind.
My back, my back, my back!
You smeared mud everywhere.
Let's wipe.
What do you do?
Go clean somewhere else.
I'm still going to wipe
out the entire castle.
Do not prevent me from doing my job.
Go away!
I told you I would clean everywhere.
Good job, Cerkutay!
There are still a lot of places to
clean up and a lot of doors to open.
Let's go.
Yes.
Can I come in, Mother Sultan?
Come in, Celali.
Soldiers are ready at
your command, Mother Sultan.
They meet secretly in the woods.
Are the soldiers who
will enter İnegöl with me ready?
I've established a unit of guards skilled
in the use of swords, Mother Sultan.
Good.
Why are you still here, Celali?
Say, say it, Celali.
Standing with Osman...
We know Nayman.
Is it a correct decision, Mother Sultan?
I don't stand on anyone's side, Celali.
I'm just standing for myself.
For this reason...
If I think standing with Osman
is the right decision...
it's the right decision.
As you command, my Mother Sultan.
If Nayman gives us a better offer...
Then I'll consider that offer too, Celali.
We fought bravely at
Çamönü, my Bey.
And we came out with the
least losses we could get out of.
However...
we lost many Ghazis who fought near you...
your father, and the invader Ertuğrul.
Ghazis are our roots.
They raised our Alps and
taught them what they know.
Olof attacked our village, and
we beheaded Frigg.
We avenged for our martyrs, my Bey.
Thank Allah.
May Allah protect your hands that carry
swords and strike the necks of the oppressors.
Allah bless you, my dear Bala.
Frigg is the beginning of
the revenge we will take.
In the war we will have with them, we
won't even allow them to have wounds.
As they have killed our Ghazis on this land...
we will also make their
blood flow on this earth.
All preparations will be
completed tomorrow.
The deadline we've given to
the oppressors has expired.
We'll start moving tomorrow.
And after we raise our
banner over İnegöl...
we'll hold your wedding as promised.
My Bey.
Is the time right amidst
all these worries?
Love does not wait.
As war is a celebration, your wedding is
also a celebration, my son.
Your command, my Bey.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come in.
My Bey, Öktem Bey and
Bengi Hatun are here.
Ayşe Hatun welcomes them.
Why don't you tell me...
Sunguralp Bey?
Welcome, my sheikh, welcome.
Salam Alaikum.
Alaikum Salam.
Alaikum Salam, my sheikh.
Why doesn't it open?
It's stuck.
But we will open it.
There are voices
coming, my Bey.
Cerkutay.
Is that you, my brother?
Turgut Bey.
We've come, we'll open it.
It's stuck, be patient a bit.
We'll wait, brother.
Thank you.
Cerkutay, someone's coming, someone's coming!
Back off!
Traitors!
- Turgut Bey.
- Mashallah.
I hope you are well, brother.
Thank Allah.
I hope you are well, Ülgen Hatun.
- Thank Allah I'm fine.
- Ülgen Hatun.
We've come to our
new place, haven't we, brother?
Praise be to Allah, my Bey.
There is not much left to
raise our flag on, Inshallah.
Inshallah.
Let's go.
Come on, Alps.
My Sultan, I'm sorry, but...
I don't get it.
Whose side are we on?
Osman's side?
Or Nayman's side?
I grab both ends of the rope...
Bayındır.
But now I'm doing whatever it
takes for our independence.
Did you keep your promise?
Mother Sultan?
Is that all?
Is this all the taxes you asked for?
The rest is loaded on horses.
Now it's your turn to
keep your word, Nayman.
You will withdraw your Mongol soldiers
from Konya and from the tribes.
I want to be sure that the
people will not be harmed.
You will never be sure.
The sword will not cut your necks...
but they will always be on your neck.
You will have difficulty in
sleeping and you will sweat.
And you will remember your
disobedience, Mother Sultan.
There is no disobedience, Nayman.
My side is obvious.
I will do everything to punish Osman
for the insolence he has done to you.
I don't need you.
My hands are enough
for all the insolent.
Certainly.
Absolutely.
But allying with me won't
make you lose anything.
Well, what do I gain from this alliance?
Victory with minimal losses.
They all listen to my words.
What do you think about Osman?
I am very curious about the
punishment you will give him.
You will know it when
everyone knows it, Mother Sultan.
Send the gold behind me
to the military headquarters...
I want them all.
Be our guest.
Let us host you in the inn, Nayman.
Send the gold after me, Mother Sultan...
all of them.
My Sultan.
It would have been nice if he had
stayed, but he didn't stay and went.
Obviously, he's going to
do a really bad job.
He hides his campaign (move) as
if it were a secret.
But he knows us well, Bayındır.
He will not trust my fidelity to him
when it is about our independence.
It's obvious.
This is just the beginning, Osman.
I will demolish your caravans, your
cities and your people...
then, you!
Frigg started with the people.
Is there any news?
It is clear that her work
has dragged on.
Send soldiers to go and check the situation.
Come, nun, come.
You must be curious
as to why I called you.
This is the spoils of our
revenge on the Turks.
I want to dedicate these
for the great Jesus.
I wanted to hear your opinion.
Good, very good idea.
In my opinion, be in
church at the crack of dawn.
With those.
And bring all your soldiers.
All of them?
Everyone?
Not all of these people fit in the church.
Then bring your most skilled
and best commanders and soldiers.
Bring them to receive their
share of your prayers.
And be blessed.
This sounds good.
The mother-in-law sent word that
she would come tomorrow morning.
Nun.
We'll have to postpone our holy
issue a bit.
We'll have an important guest tomorrow.
No problem, guests are more important.
It is enough for you to come to church
after your guest is gone
If you excuse me...
I'll get some rest.
Thank Allah.
Tomorrow we have two weddings, my sheikh.
Allah bless.
You are completing half of your faith, son.
Fear Allah for the other half.
We ask for your prayers, my sheikh.
May Allah bless you.
Amen.
May Allah bless your family, which you will establish,
and your faith.
Congratulations, Oktem Bey.
Thank you, my sheikh, thank you.
Your heart is burning for your
daughter's separation on the one hand...
On the other hand...
Establishing such a great family must
please you the most...
...isn't that true?
Certainly, my sheikh.
I have one daughter.
My Lord did not give me a male child.
There was Batur.
I considered him more like a son
than a brother-in-law.
He was martyred.
But, now
I have another son.
May my Lord bless their future, my sheikh.
Amen
Amen,
Inshallah.
Amen
For two young people to
establish a new family is crucial
Our master, the Messenger of Allah...
What did he say, dears?
Marriage is my Sunnah
Whoever does not act according to
my Sunnah is not on my side”
“Marry, for I take a pride in your number
against the other communities."
Sheikh grandfather.
What is meant by number here?
What is meant is the large number of believers
whom Allah has honored with the light of Islam
These two
will marry and have children
And those children...
...will be raised with the morals of Islam
And they will carry the banner of Islam
after their mother and father
And when the Day of Judgment comes
Everyone who defended this case will gather
around the Kawthar Basin next to the Messenger of Allah.
Inshallah (if Allah permits), my sheikh.
That is what is meant by the number.
Aladdin.
I see you are very excited
about this matter.
But wait.
Wait, because it's your
brother's turn first.
I did not mean it, Osman Bey.
Anyway, however you see fit.
I know what the shahzade(prince) meant,
Osman Bey.
He was asking about the other wedding...
...Other than our son Aktemur and
our daughter Alcicek's wedding.
Didn't you say
we have two weddings tomorrow?
Dears.
Marriage is important for a believer.
War is also equally important
It is for this reason
that both are considered a wedding.
Both lead to our abundance.
With war...
We rule out the infidels.
We tell them about Islam.
Even during war,
we maintain our morals.
For this reason...
...A believer can convert the hearts
of many unbelievers in the battlefield
And he/she becomes a way for them
to be honored with Islam.
Believers multiply.
Perhaps the one who you fought against...
Sees the human morals that you have,
sees Islam in you.
And he becomes your brother in religion.
This does not apply to all of them, of course.
There are some infidels whose
hearts are darkened with sin.
They don't hear what you say.
They don't see what you show.
They do not give up on fighting
against our religion and Allah.
And for those...
Our swords and hearts will always be strong.
We will not have mercy on the oppressor.
So that we can preserve
the rights of the oppressed.
This is our case, my sheikh.
We will listen to the words of the Messenger
of Allah and we will follow his path.
- Inshallah my Bey.
- Inshallah.
That's why we want the number.
We must be many to stand up
to the oppressors.
This is what will move us forward.
This is the origin of the river that
will feed our ambitions
We are destined to be the swords
that clash for the glory of Islam.
However...
For those swords
we need a lot of hands, my sheikh
Allah bless you.
Our alps are valiant.
When they hear about the other wedding,
which is war, they do not hesitate.
But I see that...
When it comes to the actual wedding,
they are too lazy.
Their turns will come, my sheikh.
All of them will have their turns.
Let us take Inegol first.
Then we will hold a wedding for
all of them there, Inshallah.
There is no escape for them.
As you say, my Bey.
Of course, of course.
"Look at the bride."
She put henna on her hand.
"Don't say anything to her."
She will grieve and go home.
"Her door is curved"
"She looks like an angel."
"Congratulations to you bride"
May your family be happy.
"Look at the bride."
She put henna on her hand.
"Don't say anything to her."
She will grieve and go home.
"Her door is curved"
"She looks like an angel."
"Congratulations to you henna"
May your family be happy.
May your henna be blessed, my daughter
May you be blessed
My flower.
It's the hard aspect of motherhood,
Bengi Hatun.
Tell me about it, Malhun Hatun.
I feel like my liver is being ripped out.
Bengi Hatun,
don't worry
Know that I will treat your
daughter as if she is my own.
I know...
I know, Ayse Hatun.
I'm not worried but...
It's motherhood.
Yes, Hatuns.
Let's make henna for the war, shall we?
Of course.
How can a war be without henna?
Come on then.
Come here.
In the name of Allah, the most gracious, the most merciful
Swords to the fighters, henna to the sacrifice.
The sisters compete with the men
to obtain shahada.
Martyrdom is life for us
and conquest mean blood in the vein!
If you are thirsty...
So fill your heart with martyrdom!
Sisters, sisters!
Hold on to Mother Fatma's hand
The sisters compete with the men
to obtain shahada
In the name of Allah, the most gracious,
the most merciful
Allah is the greatest!
Allah listens to those who praise him!
Allah is the greatest.
Allah's peace shall be upon you.
Praise be to Allah...
... who honored
us to carry his message
Amen
And who honored us with conquests
We praise You, who has honored us
by opening many closed doors
Amen
We thank Allah who tested us by
making us lose what we gained!
Amen.
Dying is forbidden for us
before recovering what we lost!
-And this is our oath!
-Our oath!
Answer our prayers, Lord
-Amen,
-Amen, Lord
Alps, the conquest of Inegol is near.
And what we need to do is...
...to deliver Yenişehir to Osman Bey.
Let everyone know what his mission is.
Entrances and exits of the city...
...warehouses...
...and watch towers...
We increased the number of alps
at the places you said, my Bey.
Everyone go to their duty.
Yes my Bey!
Brother.
Tell me, brother.
We will win in Inegol, won't we?
This is the weakest gate, Cerkutay.
Osman Bey and his alps will deploy here.
Kutan, Acar...
Ulgen.
You will lead the soldiers into the corridor.
The Sisters of Kayi will get there
just in time.
While you crush the soldiers..
Cerkutay will open the gate for our people.
Those dogs will fall.
Never worry, Turgut Bey.
Sister Irene is so popular in the castle
that I can go anywhere without arousing suspicion.
I see that
even the dog Olof trusts you.
You and Cerkutay have been
on the side of the infidels all this time.
And if the Kayi flag will fly
over this castle...
You have a very great share in this.
Allah bless you.
Without you, we couldn't do that.
It wasn't very difficult.
But if it weren't for me,
they would have caught Cerkutay long ago
Don't speak for me, Ulgen Hatun!
Don't speak for me!
Turgut Bey knows me.
I know of course.
Cerkutay can disguise himself in a thousand ways
so that they won't find out.
But I know something else, Ulgen Hatun.
When do you want it?
Want what?
I'm thinking something,
but what do you mean?
When are you going to join The Sisters?
In my opinion, you deserve it.
I hope to join, Turgut Bey.
Let's conquer the castle first.
Right.
Come on valiants, we won't let the infidels
own this castle, for which we sacrificed.
As you order, my Bey!
I Ask forgiveness of Almighty Allah
and repent to Him!
- My Bey.
- Yes?
Inegol isn't even our war.
Why are you caring so much?
Oh, bird brain Huseyin.
That is why I am caring so much.
What is this?
This is a map.
I Ask forgiveness of Almighty Allah
and repent to Him!
This is the door through which goods enter.
Things enter and exit through here.
Keep this well in your mind.
I'm not planning a military campaign,
I'm planning an escape.
There is no one with whom we did not cooperate,
Osman, Ismahan and even Olof.
And when we see that things are not
going as we want them to.
We have to save ourselves.
I will sacrifice my life for you, my Bey.
Well, we will see on the battlefield
if that's true or not.
There are the gates.
Keep that in your mind.
The time has now come!
The swords will come out of their sheaths for Inegol!
Do not drop your sword
until you cut the head of infidels!
Are you ready to go the battlefield
with us, shoulder to shoulder, Bengi Hatun?
My heart has been burning ever since
I lost my brother, Bala.
Today is the day of revenge
Olof's time is past due.
Today is the day of revenge and the day
of the wedding at the same time, Bengi Hatun.
When we conquer Inegol Castle, we will
hold the wedding of Aktemur and the Alcicek there
Inshallah.
Where is Oktem Bey, Bengi Hatun?
He went to Marmaracik, Bala Hatun.
He'll take alps and go to Inegol.
Let's depart, Hatuns.
Let's cut the breath of the oppressors!
Hey sisters with red henna!
Today is the day of conquest. Let's go!
Marmaracik Castle.
Praise be upon you!
My alps, my valiants!
We're going to take what's ours!
We are going to take Inegol!
Bring my horse.
Mongols are coming!
The war came to us
while we were going to it!
Welcome!
Today is the day of shahada!
- Allah is eternal!
Hold the gates and be careful!
Break the gates!
Infidels!
My Bey, the gates won't bear anymore!
They are about to get in!
They are trying to break through our gates!
They want to own what is ours!
Obviously, we will be martyred today!
But we will not die without
taking them down with us!
- Allah is the greatest!
What is the reason
of your visit, Mother Sultan?
I came to remind you that you have Inegol
only thanks to me, Olof.
I don't think so, Mother Sultan.
Yes, you helped a bit.
But nothing else.
I took Inegol with my sword!
Your sword is mine
and your castle as well!
I confronted you when
you conquered Inegol back then.
You told me that you were at my service,
that what's yours was also mine.
What's up now, Olof?
Things changed, Mother Sultan.
I rose while you fell.
You can no longer rule me.
Seems that Nayman standing behind you
encouraged you a lot
Or is it that he stands against me?
Olof... Olof...
Do you think Nayman
has just allied with you?
What does this mean?
It means that you are just the owner of this
tiny castle and a commander of a weak Emperor.
We are the Seljuqs.
You can only be
a puppet of Nayman, Olof.
And when he's done with you,
you'll be the first to die.
Without my protection,
you are an easy prey for Nayman, Olof.
The army sent by Emperor Andronicus
will come to my command in a few days.
Your protection?
Only Lord protects me!
Also, if you trusted me,
if you were my friend...
You wouldn't come here armed.
Inegol was watered with the blood
of my brother Gunduz Bey.
It was protected by the sword of Turgut Bey.
But we lost it due to
the traitors among us!
If we pursued the revenge...
Or if we pursued wealth, we would have
conquered it 20 times by now!
But everything has a right time.
But everything has a right time!
And for Inegol,
the time has come.
When Turgut Bey opens the gates...
You will strike the archers first.
We are going to protect our alps
inside and outside.
And when the soldiers approach the door,
Hatuns will begin to cross the tunnel.
We will shoot arrows to the soldiers.
They won't understand where we are.
Always remember!
We show mercy to those who ask for forgiveness.
But when they raise their swords, be a lion!
My Alps.
I won't kill you now.
You think you're very smart, Olof.
You're right, I am armed.
Because there is Osman
who attacks everywhere like a madman.
We don't know whom he will attack.
Is there something
you want to say, Mother Sultan?
I just wanted to explain
why I am armed.
I am safe in my castle in Inegol.
But I might get caught in a trap
when I get out of here.
Do you still think you own my castle?
If it isn't for me protecting your castle...
you will be kiled either by
Naiman or by Osman one day, Olof.
Nobody can kill me.
I am invincible.
Inegol is my castle
The Byzantine army will come from one side,
and my brothers from the north!
I lost a lot in these lands!
I will not share my winnings with anyone!
- If you don't share, you won't have anything left.
- Enough, enough!
I forgive you today for
helping me in the past!
Now...
Get out of my castle...
Right now!
Well, I told you my opinion, I warned you.
You did not greet me when I came.
Accompany us at least
to the yard as we leave, Olof
Kayi Hatuns will enter the den
of infidels today!
And when the gates open,
we too will go inside
Don't forget,
no one will run towards death today!
No one will endanger the victory today!
We have the numbers today!
We are the strong ones today!
Absolute victory will be ours!
Do we still have the numbers while
Ismahan and Bayindir are inside?
No, we left them no other choice
but to join us.
They want Olof's head more than we do!
They know that if Olof's head doesn't fall,
they will fall!
Do not forget! We may be at the same side
with them in this war...
But we have still an account to settle.
But we will hold Olof accountable first,
and then we will hold them accountable
As you command, my Bey!
Alps!
- May our conquest be blessed!
- Amen
Allah is the greatest!
Allah is the greatest! Allah is the greatest!
We got close to the corridor,
we have to be careful now!
Time is short, we have to cross the corridor
before the soldiers arrive!
Don't rush, Bengi Hatun!
Ulgen will open the way for us.
Come on, sisters, hurry up, come on!
Hurry! Now! Hurry!
- Hurry!
Where are you sisters?
Ulgen!
I will open, sisters, I will open!
Be patient!
Traitors!
Welcome!
- Thank Allah.
- Greetings, Ulgen!
Welcome,
you brought joy!
Welcome.
You barely did it!
Welcome!
- Thank you.
- Welcome.
Come on Hatuns
the arena is ours now!
Sisters, do not let them!
Come on sisters!
This way!
The Turks are coming!
To the walls!
Close the doors!
- Come quickly!
- Archers!
It's time for us to fulfill our duty!
What's happening here?
- I told you that I'd come, Olof.
- You ignobles!
I told you you would lose
if you didn't share, Olof!
Gates! Gates!
I am here, Cerkutay!
Alps!
What are you doing here?
I came to save you.
I came to kill them!
Gates!
Cerkutay!
For the country!
Gates!
We'll break the gates!
Come on alps!
Praise be!
Let's go!
Cerkutay!
O Allah!
Osman!
Cerkutay!
What did you do to Cerkutay?
Cerkutay, Cerkutay.
Let's go.
Cerkutay.
Don't ever think about pronouncing
the shahada.
You will teach me how to use sword!
What else can I teach you?
You killed them all already.
Cerkutay, come on, open your eyes!
Cerkutay is strong!
Cerkutay won't die!
Cerkutay, don't go!
I'll cook for you!
Cerkutay!
This is my castle, Osman!
I am not like the people before me!
What you are waiting for is your end only!
Your cruelty has brought your death!
Nothing will stand in our way!
We will sacrifice our lives if necessary!
We're not going anywhere
until we take Inegol!
Praise be!
I gave birth to a girl
braver than men!
She is like her mother!
I mean mother in law!
- Come on, Hatuns!
- Come on!
Come on, this direction!
Come to me, ignobles!
Alcicek!
I owe you my soul, Subasi.
You owe nothing.
Our lives are one.
Let's go.
Do you miss your country, Acar brother?
I don't know if he missed or not,
but he certainly missed the battle!
Thank you, brother!
I can't keep protecting you, brother!
Protect your back!
Okay!
I couldn't protect you!
Cerkutay!
He lost a lot of blood, Boran.
Oh brother, Cerkutay!
Nothing will happen to Cerkutay!
Kumral Abdal!
Cerkutay!
Kumaral Abdal!
- Cerkutay!
- He's hurt a lot!
Hold on, brother.
Alps! Alps!
- Come on!
- Come on, come on!
Let's go!
Come on, Cerkutay!
Come on brothers!
Cerkutay! Cerkutay!
Cerkutay!
This will end right here, right now Olof!
No capturing!
No prison!
There is only death!
That's why I'm not going alone!
You will not be alone!
Frigg will be waiting for you there!
I'll send you there now!
No!
You oppressed many innocents!
You oppressed many orphans!
Your death will brind justice!
Come here.
Come on, come on!
You and those with you,
all of you, this will be the end of you!
What is ours, will remain ours!
What's left for you...
...is only death!
Thank Allah.
Thank Lord.
Allah is the greatest!
You jackals!
Come here, ignoble dogs!
We'll send you to hell!
Bala Hatun!
So we were destined to fight
back to back, Ismahan Sultan!
What's past is past, Bala Hatun!
Now we unite, but what if you stab us
from behind tomorrow?
If one day I point my dagger at you,
you will see it, Malhun Hatun.
The same goes for you too, Ismahan Sultan.
The same goes for you.
We don't fight for the fame.
We do not rise our swords
for wealth.
The property we take is
for the cause of world order!
We take property to destroy the infidels!
Do not forget.
Wealth is only for the mortal life.
It will remain an inheritance
for our generation.
But whoever tries to take our inheritance...
Whoever takes our inheritance...
Then...
They won't be resting.
Nor will be sleeping.
Long live Osman Bey!
Mother, what happened?
I'm not comfortable, Alcicek.
Your father is late, something is wrong.
My valiant, he is always the first
one to appear when it is about war.
Don't worry mother,
he'll come if Alalh permits.
Bring that dog!
Not one of you...
But even if one thousnad of you faced me...
I will never back down from the case of Allah!
Even if you all unite against me...
Your end will be the same.
I fought all my life.
I finished thousands like you.
Byzantium will turn this land into hell.
You got stuck between Neiman and Andronikos
Your death is near Osman.
Your death is near.
For those who walk for our cause,
death is always near.
Death is our compass.
And shahada is a wedding for us.
But...
Your head will fall off today.
My Bey!
Nayman is coming!
You are not brave enough to kill
Nayman's friend in front of him.
We both hunted well today, Osman.
- Father!
- Oktem!
Oktem.
This fool...
He thinks he can kill me, Nayman!
He is mistaken.
Just like the Mother next to him!
She also chose the wrong side!
She offered me gold first
Now she is offering me her head.
I didn't chose the wrong side!
I turned back from the wrong side, Nayman!
Osman.
If you don't care about Oktem's life.
Kill Olof.
Bengi.
What are we fighting for?
My Bey?
For the cause of Allah.
Why are our men martyred?
In order to rule the world!
And for what the living live?
For The Red Apple
(Symbol of the ideas and desiers of Turks)
So...
This old wolf...
...has to die today.
No, Osman Bey.
Do not cosider my life equal
with that dog's life.
He is just a dog while I yearn for shahada.
You will let Olof free, Osman.
Otherwise...
Oktem will be only a beginning.
I will not stop until I destroy you as a whole.
Make an agreement.
We wanted to take the castle and we did.
We kill Olof later.
No.
Don't do it, Osman.
He will die today.
Don't Osman, don't.
There is only one idea
we are loyal to.
Mercy to the cruel...
...is an insult to the innocents.
Your sword won't just kill Olof...
It will also kill Oktem.
You are right.
But with one difference.
If Olof dies, he will be a cadaver
If Oktem Bey dies,
he will become a martyr
Tell me!
Is there anyone who fears death?
No my Bey!
No.
No, my Bey.
Now look at Olof very well.
Very well.
And see how he ends up.
I bear witness that there is no god but Allah
And I bear witness that Muhammad is
His servant and Messenger
We belong to Allah and to Him we shall return
What you just did...
...will be your end, Osman.
We will all die.
But I swear that...
I will not die before I kill you.
Visit our website for more: turkision.com